Guide to the Henry Savage Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Other Papers, 1900-1980; 4.63; (6 boxes)
  - Printed ephemera removed from address book, undated (Box 10)
  - Stamp removed from address book, undated (Box 10)
  - Two "una peseta" notes removed from address book, 1951, 1953 (Box 10)